Guide to the Southeast Women's Employment Coalition Records, 1868-1991 bulk (1981-1990)
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Subject Files Series, 1868-1988, undated (bulk 1982-1987) (Box 52)
  Correspondence, clippings, financial papers, and reports. Arranged in alphabetical order by topic.
  - Affirmative action, 1981-1987 (Box 52)
  - Appalachia, 1978-1984 (Box 52)
  - Attitudes, opinion, 1981-1984 (Box 52)
  - Black business, 1981-1983 (Box 52)
  - Black community, 1982-1986 (Box 53)
  - Black families, 1981-1984 (Box 53)
  - Black workers, 1981-1985 (Box 53)
  - Boll weevils, 1982 (Box 53)
  - Budget reductions, 1981-1985 (Box 53)
  - Business trends, 1981-1985 (Box 53)
  - Child abuse, 1984 (Box 53)
  - Child care: (Box 53)
    - 1983-1985 (Box 53)
    - Employer initiatives, 1983 (Box 53)
  - Civil rights, 1981-1985 (Box 53)
  - Clerical workers, 1981-1984 (Box 53)
  - Coalition clips, 1980-1986 (Box 53)
  - Comparable worth, 1980-1986 (Box 53)
  - Construction: General data, 1980-1988 (Box 53)
  - Construction: Tradeswomen, 1987 (Box 53)
  - Corporate strategies, 1982 (Box 53)
  - Democrats: Politics, 1982-1986 (Box 53)
  - Disabled, handicapped, 1981-1985 (Box 53)
  - Discrimination lawsuits, 1980-1988 (Box 53)
  - Displaced workers, 1983 (Box 53)
  - Economic trends, 1979-1985 (Box 53)
  - Economy, 1980-1982 (Box 53)
  - Education, 1985 (Box 53)
  - Election analysis, 1982, Nov. (Box 53)
  - Employee benefits, 1981-1984 (Box 53)
  - Employment surveys on women, 1981-1984 (Box 53)
  - Enterprise zones, 1982 (Box 53)
  - Equal Rights Amendment, 1981-1985 (Box 53)
  - Executive branch: National politics, 1981-1985 (Box 53)
  - Fair Employment Law, 1981-1983 (Box 53)
  - Famous personalities, 1980-1985 (Box 53)
  - Government spending, 1984 (Box 53)
  - High technology jobs, 1983-1984 (Box 53)
  - Highway construction: (Box 53)
    - 1980-1986, (2 folders) (Box 53)
    - Outlook, 1984-1985 (Box 53)
  - Human Rights of Africa and America, 1988 (Box 53)
  - Integration, segregation, 1981-1982 (Box 53)
  - International women, 1981-1984 (Box 53)
  - Jackson Primary rules challenge, 1983-1984 (Box 53)
  - Job bills, 1982-1984 (Box 53)
  - Kentucky women, 1977-1988 (Box 53)
  - Labor force trends, 1982-1985 (Box 53)
  - Labor relations, 1986-1987 (Box 53)
  - Labor unions, 1979-1985 (Box 53)
  - Latin America, 1983 (Box 53)
  - Military spending, 1982-1985 (Box 53)
  - Military women, 1981-1985 (Box 53)
  - New Federalism, 1981-1983 (Box 54)
  - Nontraditional work for women (excluding highway construction), 1981-1985 (Box 54)
  - Nursing home/Healthcare issues, 1982-1985 (Box 54)
  - Occupational safety and health, 1980-1984 (Box 54)
  - Older women, 1983 (Box 54)
  - Parker-Coltrane Political Action Committee, 1981-1982 (Box 54)
  - Penn School Heritage Celebration, 1986 (Box 54)
  - Plant closings, 1982-1984 (Box 54)
  - Political race, 1983-1984 (Box 54)
  - Poultry, 1987 (Box 54)
  - Poverty, 1979-1987 (Box 54)
  - Racism: Contemporary stories, 1981-1984 (Box 54)
  - Redistricting, 1981-1982 (Box 54)
  - Religion, 1985-1986 (Box 54)
  - Republicans, 1981-1985 (Box 54)
  - Restaurant workers, 1982-1984 (Box 54)
  - The Revolution copies, 1868 (Box 54)
  - Rural women, 1980-1982 (Box 54)
  - Sexual harassment, 1980-1987 (Box 54)
  - Single parents, 1984 (Box 54)
  - The South: Economics and politics, 1980-1986 (Box 54)
  - Sri Lanka, undated (Box 54)
  - Supreme Court, 1980-1986 (Box 54)
  - Unemployment, 1981-1984 (Box 54)
  - Unions, 1986-1987 (Box 54)
  - Voting Rights Act, 1981-1985 (Box 54)
  - The Welfare State, 1981-1985 (Box 54)
  - Women and theology, 1982-1985 (Box 54)
  - Women as an electorate: Gender gap politics, 1980-1987 (Box 54)
  - Women executives, 1980-1984 (Box 54)
  - Women in government, 1981-1985 (Box 54)
  - Women in road construction, 1980-1985 (Box 54)
  - Women of color, 1981-1985 (Box 54)
  - Women's issues, 1978-1980 (Box 54)
  - Workfare '84, 1976-1984 (Box 54)
  - Youth employment, 1984 (Box 54)
  - Zimbabwe, 1983 (Box 54)
- Conference Files Series, 1983-1989, undated (Box 54)
  Correspondence, brochures, conference evaluations, conference keepsakes, financial reports, and mailing lists, relating to various conferences the Southeast Women's Employment Coalition sponsored or with which it had contact. The bulk of the series concerns the Southeast Women's Employment Coalition conferences held in 1984 and 1989. Arranged in alphabetical order by name of conference.
  - Center for Women's Economic Alternatives, 1988 (Box 54)
  - Economic Conference brochures, 1988-1989 (Box 54)
  - Eighth School for Union Women, 1986 (Box 54)
  - Kentucky Tradeswomen meeting, 1986-1987 (Box 54)
  - Leadership Skills for Union Women, 1985 (Box 54)
  - Leadership skills: Louisville workshop (Jan. 1, 1988), 1987-1988 (Box 54)
  - Nairobi Women's Conference, 1985, July (Box 54)
  - National Tradeswomen's Conference (Box 55)
    - 1985-1987, (3 folders) (Box 55)
    - Evaluation of the First National Tradeswomen's Conference, 1983 (Box 55)
  - Seminar on Comparable Worth Research, 1983 (Box 55)
  - Southeast Women's Employment Coalition Leadership Conference, 1984: (Box 55)
    - Ad/Program book, 1984 (Box 55)
    - Agenda/Schedule, 1984 (Box 55)
    - Brochure, 1984 (Box 55)
    - Child care, 1984 (Box 55)
    - Correspondence: (Box 55)
      - Incoming, 1984-1985 (Box 55)
      - Outgoing, 1984 (Box 55)
    - Entertainment, 1984 (Box 55)
    - Evaluations, 1985 (Box 55)
    - Facilitation, 1984, (2 folders) (Box 55)
    - Financial information, 1984 (Box 55)
    - Information requests, 1984 (Box 55)
    - Internal barrier's meeting, 1984 (Box 55)
    - Mexican women, 1984 (Box 55)
    - Montreat facility, 1984 (Box 55)
    - On-site job list, 1984 (Box 55)
    - Planning, 1984-1985 (Box 55)
    - Planning Committee, 1984-1985 (Box 55)
    - Presentation: Jo Carson, 1984 (Box 55)
    - Recruitment, resource people, 1984 (Box 55)
    - Registration, 1984-1985 (Box 55)
    - Scholarship list and support requests, 1984 (Box 55)
    - Southern black and white women's connection, 1985 (Box 55)
    - Miscellaneous, 1984, (2 folders) (Box 56)
  - Southeast Women's Employment Coalition Leadership Conference, 1989: (Box 56)
    - Book 1, 1989, (4 folders) (Box 56)
    - Book 2, 1988-1989, (3 folders) (Box 56)
    - Call for Workshops, 1988-1989 (Box 56)
    - Correspondence, 1988 (Box 56)
    - Documents/Publicity, 1989 (Box 56)
    - Entertainment, 1989 (Box 56)
    - Evaluations, 1989 (Box 56)
    - Expenses, 1989 (Box 56)
    - Florida Low Income Housing Coalition, 1988-1989 (Box 56)
    - Large and small group sessions, 1989 (Box 56)
    - Logo and t-shirt designs, 1989 (Box 56)
    - Mailing lists, 1989 (Box 56)
    - Planning Committee, 1988-1989, (2 folders) (Box 56)
    - Program book, 1989 (Box 56)
    - Recruiters, 1988-1989 (Box 56)
    - Registrants, 1989, (2 folders) (Box 56)
    - Scholarship fund, 1988-1989 (Box 57)
    - Site information, 1989 (Box 57)
    - Workers' information, 1989 (Box 57)
    - Miscellaneous, 1988-1989 (Box 57)
  - Southern School for Union Women Conference, 1986 (Box 57)
  - Women and Economic Justice Conference, 1985 (Box 57)
  - Women on the Move: Economic Justice, 1988 (Box 57)
  - Women's Project: Women and Work Conference, 1986-1988, (2 folders) (Box 57)
- Organizations Series, 1981-1989, undated (bulk 1984-1988) (Box 57)
  Notes, reports, and brochures pertaining to organizations, some of them created to improve the status of women. Arranged in alphabetical order.
  - American Friends Service Committee, 1990 (Box 57)
  - Appalachian Regional School for Church Leaders, 1986-1987 (Box 57)
  - Apprenticeship Program in Kentucky: Nontraditional Crafts, 1988-1989 (Box 57)
  - Association for Community Based Education, 1986-1987 (Box 57)
  - Australia. New South Wales Department of Industrial Relations and Employment. Women's Directorate, 1987-1991. (Box 57)
  - Bennington Corporation, 1987 (Box 57)
  - Center for Business and Economic Research, 1987 (Box 57)
  - Center for Community Change, 1983 (Box 57)
  - Center for Research on Women: Memphis State University, Tennessee, 1982-1987 (Box 57)
  - Center for Rural Affairs: Training Curriculum for Farmers, 1988 (Box 57)
  - Charleston, South Carolina Group, 1988 (Box 57)
  - Church Women United, 1983-1985 (Box 57)
  - Coalition of Labor Union Women, 1988 (Box 57)
  - Coalition on Human Needs, 1989 (Box 57)
  - Displaced Homemaker Network, 1981-1987 (Box 57)
  - Ecumenical Review Board, 1985-1987 (Box 57)
  - Farmworkers Self-help, Inc., 1984-1988 (Box 57)
  - Federation of Child Care Center, undated (Box 57)
  - Highlander Center, 1984-1986 (Box 57)
  - Institute for Southern Studies, 1986-1987 (Box 57)
  - Justice for Women Working Group, 1984-1985 (Box 57)
  - Kentucky: (Box 57)
    - Commission on Women, 1987 (Box 57)
    - Department of Education (Vocational Education), 1982-1987 (Box 57)
    - Lexington Tradeswomen, 1988-1989 (Box 57)
    - State Apprenticeship and Training Council, 1988-1989 (Box 57)
    - Women Advocates, 1986-1988 (Box 57)
  - MDC, Inc., 1982-1986 (Box 57)
  - Missouri Tradeswomen, 1986-1987, undated (Box 57)
  - Mountain Women's Exchange, 1987 (Box 57)
  - National Association for the Advancement of Colored People Legal Defense and Educational Fund, 1984, Feb.-Apr., (2 folders) (Box 57)
  - National Coalition on Black Voter Participation, Inc., 1983 (Box 58)
  - Older Women's League, 1986-1988 (Box 58)
  - Operating Engineers Apprenticeship and Training Program, 1989 (Box 58)
  - Public Affairs Research and Communications, Inc., 1985-1986 (Box 58)
  - Preparatory Recruitment Employment Program, 1986 (Box 58)
  - Restaurant Employees Association of Lexington, Ky., 1983 (Box 58)
  - Sea Island Youth Development Corps, 1987-1988 (Box 58)
  - Southern Growth Policies Board, 1984-1986, (2 folders) (Box 58)
  - Taxpayers Advocacy and Support Coalition, 1988-1989 (Box 58)
  - Toyota, 1986-1987 (Box 58)
  - Tradeswomen, Inc., 1986-1988 (Box 58)
  - Tri-State Network, 1987 (Box 58)
  - Tuskegee University, 1986 (Box 58)
  - Urban County Council: Meeting agendas, 1988 (Box 58)
  - Women and Employment, Inc., 1981-1984 (Box 58)
  - Women for Economic Justice, 1982-1984 (Box 58)
  - Women's Bureau: United States. Department of Labor, 1986-1988 (Box 58)
  - Young Women's Christian Association Women in Trades Project: Memphis, Tenn., 1989 (Box 58)
  - Miscellaneous, 1986-1989 (Box 58)
- Printed Material Series, 1969-1990, undated (bulk 1973-1988) (Box 58)
  Reports, brochures, and newsletters. Arranged into two subseries, Chronological (by date of publication) and Alphabetical (by first letter of publication title). See addition to this series at end of container list.
  - Chronological Subseries (Box 58)
    - 1973-1979, undated, (9 folders) (Box 58)
    - 1970s-1983, (14 folders) (Box 59)
    - 1983-1987, (15 folders) (Box 60)
    - 1987-1990, undated, (10 folders) (Box 61)
  - Alphabetical Subseries (Box 61)
    - A, 1983-1989, (3 folders) (Box 61)
    - B, 1972-1989 (Box 61)
    - C, 1969-1988 (Box 61)
    - C, 1969-1988, (5 folders) (Box 62)
    - D, 1984-1988 (Box 62)
    - E, 1976-1988, (2 folders) (Box 62)
    - F, 1983-1988 (Box 62)
    - G, 1982-1990 (Box 62)
    - H, 1983-1988 (Box 62)
    - I, 1979-1990, (2 folders) (Box 62)
    - J-K, 1982-1988 (Box 62)
    - L, 1982-1987, (2 folders) (Box 62)
    - M, 1983-1989, (3 folders) (Box 63)
    - N, 1982-1990, (5 folders) (Box 63)
    - O-P, 1982-1989 (Box 63)
    - P, 1982-1989 (Box 63)
    - R, 1978-1988, (2 folders) (Box 63)
    - S, 1976-1988, (4 folders) (Box 63)
    - S, 1976-1988 (Box 64)
    - T, 1978-1989, (3 folders) (Box 64)
    - U-V, 1982-1988 (Box 64)
    - W, 1974-1988, (5 folders) (Box 64)
    - X-Y-Z, and miscellaneous, 1983-1985 (Box 64)
- Pictures Series, 1956-1989, undated (bulk 1980-1986) (Box 64)
  Chiefly photographs of various events and activities sponsored by the Southeast Women's Employment Coalition. Subdivided into four subseries, Photographs, Photographs and Negatives, Negatives, and Miscellaneous Formats. The first three subseries are arranged alphabetically by topic under each category, then chronologically.
  - Photographs Subseries (Box 64)
    - Conferences and Meetings: (Box 64)
      - Leadership Training Convention, Denver, Colo., 1984, May (Box 64)
      - Southeast Women's Employment Coalition: (Box 64)
        - 1980, Dec. 1-3 (Box 64)
        - 1984, Dec. (Box 64)
        - Leadership Conference, 1989, (2 folders) (Box 64)
      - Southern Rural Women's Network, 1981 (Box 64)
      - Women Miners, 1980 (Box 64)
      - Women's Work-Women's Lives, 1984 (Box 64)
    - County Market photos for summer 1985 newsletter, 1985, Aug. (Box 64)
    - Ford Foundation, undated (Box 64)
    - Hawkins, Martha, 1984, July (Box 64)
    - Midwest Women's Center, undated (Box 64)
    - National Press Conference, Washington, D.C., 1985 (Box 64)
    - Southeast Women's Employment Coalition: Birthday party, undated (Box 64)
    - United States. Department Of Transportation, Washington, D.C., 1984, Oct. (Box 64)
    - Working women, undated (Box 64)
    - Workplaces, undated (Box 64)
    - 1980, Nov.-1987, undated, (7 folders) (Box 64)
    - undated, (8 folders) (Box 65)
  - Photographs and Negatives Subseries (Box 65)
    - Cincinnati Reds Game, 1984, Aug. (Box 65)
    - Conferences and Meetings: (Box 65)
      - National Conference of Women and Miners, 6th Annual, 1984, Sept. (Box 65)
      - National Tradeswomen, 1987, May 2-3 (Box 65)
      - Native American Women: Swaner Hunt, 1985, June (Box 65)
      - Southeast Women's Employment Coalition, 1987, undated, (2 folders) (Box 65)
        - Board, 1986, Mar. (Box 65)
        - Leadership Conference, 1989 (Box 65)
        - Steering Committee, 1986, Oct. (Box 65)
        - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 65)
    - Hardhatted Women of Kentucky and Geraldine Ferraro, 1984, Sept. (Box 65)
    - Hilton Head, S.C., 1985? (Box 65)
    - Homeless shelter, Atlanta, Ga., 1987, Aug. (Box 65)
    - Labor Subcommittee on Women in Nontraditional Work Hearings, Washington, D.C., 1987, Nov. (Box 65)
    - Massik, Sue: Art's Place, 1987, Oct. (Box 65)
    - Ms. Foundation, undated (Box 65)
    - Solidarity 1199, 1984 (Box 65)
    - Southeast Women's Employment Coalition cover, undated (Box 65)
    - Tourism, undated (Box 65)
    - Valley construction, undated (Box 65)
    - Women in construction work, undated (Box 65)
    - 1956-1984, undated, (12 folders) (Box 65)
  - Negatives Subseries (Box 65)
    - Beartooth Mountain and Native American Women, undated (Box 65)
    - Center for Community Change, undated (Box 65)
    - Coal Miners' Tour: Rose Muraa and Company, Eastern Kentucky, undated (Box 65)
    - Coal mining tour, 1982, July (Box 65)
    - Conferences and Meetings: (Box 65)
      - Economics Training Workshop, Savannah Penn Center, 1983, June 17 (Box 65)
      - Highland? 1980, June (Box 65)
      - Job Partnership Training Act Workshop, 1983, Feb. 18 (Box 65)
      - Leadership Training, Knoxville, Tenn., 1982, Jan. (Box 65)
      - Niagara Falls Blue Mountain jobs, 1982, Sept.-Oct. (Box 65)
      - Old Salt, undated (Box 65)
      - Southeast Women's Employment Coalition Board: 1982, June (Box 65)
      - Southeast Women's Employment Coalition Board: Camp Wendy Woods, 1983, Jan. (Box 65)
      - Washington D.C., 1982 (Box 65)
      - Women in construction, 1981, Apr. (Box 65)
      - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 65)
    - Cove Mountain Lodge, Tenn., 1982, Nov. (Box 65)
    - Highlander Anniversary, 1982, Mar. 8 (Box 65)
    - New York trip: Fundraising, 1982, July (Box 65)
    - Painting the Phillis Wheatley Young Women's Christian Association Center in Atlanta, Ga., undated (Box 65)
    - Road construction, undated (Box 65)
    - State Fair: Blue Collar Women, 1984, June (Box 65)
    - Washington D.C. trip, 1987, Nov. (Box 65)
    - 1983, Sept., undated, (2 folders) (Box 65)
  - Miscellaneous Formats Subseries (Box 65)
    - Miscellaneous formats, 1986, undated (Box 65)
      - Seneca Falls, N.Y., undated (Box 65)
- Audio Visual Series, 1963-1990, undated(bulk 1981-1990) (Box 66-68)
  Subdivided into three subseries: Audiocassettes, Filmstrips, and Videocassettes, chiefly pertaining to meetings and conferences sponsored by the Southeast Women's Employment Coalition. Audiocassettes comprise the bulk of the series. Both audiocassettes and videocassettesare are further subdivided into Southeast Women's Employment Coalition sponsored activities and non-Southeast Women's Employment Coalition activities. Audiocassettes in the Southeast Women's Employment Coalition activities subseries are arranged chronologically, while audiocassettes in the non-Southeast Women's Employment Coalition activities subseries are arranged chronologically and then alphabetically by title.
  - Audiocassettes Subseries (Box 66-68)
    - Southeast Women's Employment Coalition Sponsored Activities, Chronological (Box 66-68)
      - 1980: WHUR News Report (Box 66, Case 1, Audio-cassette 80-1)
      - 1981 July 9: Affirmative Action Meeting (Box 66, Case 1, Audio-cassette 81-1)
      - 1981 Summer: Unions/Nontraditional Jobs Meeting (Box 66, Case 1, Audio-cassette 81-2)
      - 1981 Oct. 31: Organizing Strategies for Issues of Unemployment and Economic Strategies for Women (Box 66, Case 1, Audio-cassette 81-3)
      - 1981 Nov. 14: Southern Rural Women's Network Conference, Epes, Ala. (Box 66, Case 1, Audio-cassette 81-4)
      - 1981 Nov. 14: Southern Rural Women's Network Conference, Epes, Ala. (Box 66, Case 1, Audio-cassette 81-5)
      - 1981 Nov. 14: Southern Rural Women's Network Conference, Epes, Ala. (Box 66, Case 1, Audio-cassette 81-6)
      - 1981 Nov. 14: Southern Rural Women's Network Conference, Epes, Ala. (Box 66, Case 1, Audio-cassette 81-7)
      - 1981? Discussion, Reagan Budget and Women, National Women's Law Center (Box 66, Case 1, Audio-cassette 81-8)
      - 1981: Meeting to discuss hearings (Box 66, Case 1, Audio-cassette 81-9)
      - 1982 Jan. 23: Southern Rural Women's Network, Selma, Ala. (Box 66, Case 1, Audio-cassette 82-1)
      - 1982 Jan. 23: Southern Rural Women's Network, Selma, Ala. (Box 66, Case 1, Audio-cassette 82-2)
      - 1982 Jan. 23: Southern Rural Women's Network, Selma, Ala. (Box 66, Case 1, Audio-cassette 82-3)
      - 1982 Jan. 30: Leadership Training Meeting, Knoxville, Tenn. (Box 66, Case 1, Audio-cassette 82-4)
      - 1982 Jan. 30: Leadership Training Meeting, Knoxville, Tenn. (Box 66, Case 1, Audio-cassette 82-5)
      - 1982, Jan. 30: Leadership Training Meeting, Knoxville, Tenn. (Box 66, Case 2, Audio-cassette 82-6)
      - 1982 Apr. 2: Women Writers Conference: Cherrie Moraga and Barbara Smith (Box 66, Case 2, Audio-cassette 82-7)
      - 1982 May 15: Leadership Organizing Workshop: Southeast (Box 66, Case 2, Audio-cassette 82-8)
      - 1982 May 15: Leadership Organizing Workshop: Southeast (Box 66, Case 2, Audio-cassette 82-9)
      - 1982 May 15: Leadership Organizing Workshop: Southeast (Box 66, Case 2, Audio-cassette 82-10)
      - 1982 June 10-11: Women's Employment Coalition Board Meeting (Box 66, Case 2, Audio-cassette 82-11)
      - 1982 June 10-11: Women's Employment Coalition Board Meeting (Box 66, Case 2, Audio-cassette 82-12)
      - 1982 June 10-11: Women's Employment Coalition Board Meeting (Box 66, Case 2, Audio-cassette 82-13)
      - 1982 June 10-11: Women's Employment Coalition Board Meeting (Box 66, Case 2, Audio-cassette 82-14)
      - 1982 Sept. 14-15: Southeast Women's Employment Coalition Board Meeting (Box 66, Case 2, Audio-cassette 82-15)
      - 1982 Sept. 14-15: Southeast Women's Employment Coalition Board Meeting (Box 66, Case 2, Audio-cassette 82-16)
      - 1982 Sept. 14-15: Southeast Women's Employment Coalition Board Meeting (Box 66, Case 2, Audio-cassette 82-17)
      - 1982 Sept. 14-15: Southeast Women's Employment Coalition Board Meeting (Box 66, Case 2, Audio-cassette 82-18)
      - 1982 Sept. 14-15: Southeast Women's Employment Coalition Board Meeting (Box 66, Case 2, Audio-cassette 82-19)
      - 1982 Sept. 14-15: Southeast Women's Employment Coalition Board Meeting (Box 66, Case 2, Audio-cassette 82-20)
      - 1982 Nov. 12-14: Leadership Training (Box 66, Case 3, Audio-cassette 82-21)
      - 1982 Nov. 12-14: Leadership Training (Box 66, Case 3, Audio-cassette 82-22)
      - 1982 Nov. 12-14: Leadership Training (Box 66, Case 3, Audio-cassette 82-23)
      - 1982 Nov.: Rose Muraa, University of Kentucky, Lexington, Ky. (Box 66, Case 3, Audio-cassette 82-24)
      - 1982 Dec. 7-8: Southeast Women's Employment Coalition Board Meeting (Box 66, Case 3, Audio-cassette 82-25)
      - 1982 Dec. 7-8: Southeast Women's Employment Coalition Board Meeting (Box 66, Case 3, Audio-cassette 82-26)
      - 1982 Dec. 7-8: Southeast Women's Employment Coalition Board Meeting (Box 66, Case 3, Audio-cassette 82-27)
      - 1982 Dec. 7-8: Southeast Women's Employment Coalition Board Meeting (Box 66, Case 3, Audio-cassette 82-28)
      - 1982 Dec. 7-8: Southeast Women's Employment Coalition Board Meeting (Box 66, Case 3, Audio-cassette 82-29)
      - 1982 Dec. 7-8: Southeast Women's Employment Coalition Board Meeting (Box 66, Case 3, Audio-cassette 82-30)
      - 1983 Mar. 6-8: Southeast Women's Employment Coalition Board Meeting (Box 66, Case 3, Audio-cassette 83-1)
      - 1983 Mar. 6-8: Southeast Women's Employment Coalition Board Meeting (Box 66, Case 3, Audio-cassette 83-2)
      - 1983 Mar. 6-8: Southeast Women's Employment Coalition Board Meeting (Box 66, Case 3, Audio-cassette 83-3)
      - 1983 Mar. 16-18: Leadership Workshop, Washington, D.C. (Box 66, Case 3, Audio-cassette 83-4)
      - 1983 June 15-17: Economics Workshop (Box 66, Case 3, Audio-cassette 83-5)
      - 1983 June 15-17: Economics Workshop (Box 66, Case 4, Audio-cassette 83-6)
      - 1983 June 15-17: Economics Workshop (Box 66, Case 4, Audio-cassette 83-7)
      - 1983 June 15-17: Economics Workshop (Box 66, Case 4, Audio-cassette 83-8)
      - 1983 June 15-17: Economics Workshop (Box 66, Case 4, Audio-cassette 83-9)
      - 1983 June 15-17: Economics Workshop (Box 66, Case 4, Audio-cassette 83-10)
      - 1983 Sept. 10: Southeast Women's Employment Coalition Board Meeting (Box 66, Case 4, Audio-cassette 83-11)
      - 1983 Nov. 19: Southeast Women's Employment Coalition Meeting, Durham, N.C. (Box 66, Case 4, Audio-cassette 83-12)
      - 1983 Nov. 19: Southeast Women's Employment Coalition Meeting, Durham, N.C. (Box 66, Case 4, Audio-cassette 83-13)
      - 1983 Nov. 19: Southeast Women's Employment Coalition Meeting, Durham, N.C. (Box 66, Case 4, Audio-cassette 83-14)
      - 1983 Nov. 19: Southeast Women's Employment Coalition Meeting, Durham, N.C. (Box 66, Case 4, Audio-cassette 83-15)
      - 1983 Dec. 6-8: Southeast Women's Employment Coalition Board Meeting (Box 66, Case 4, Audio-cassette 83-16)
      - 1983 Dec. 6-8: Southeast Women's Employment Coalition Board Meeting (Box 66, Case 4, Audio-cassette 83-17)
      - 1983 Dec. 6-8: Southeast Women's Employment Coalition Board Meeting (Box 66, Case 4, Audio-cassette 83-18)
      - 1983 Dec. 6-8: Southeast Women's Employment Coalition Board Meeting (Box 66, Case 4, Audio-cassette 83-19)
      - 1983 Dec. 6-8: Southeast Women's Employment Coalition Board Meeting (Box 66, Case 4, Audio-cassette 83-20)
      - 1983 Dec. 6-8: Southeast Women's Employment Coalition Board Meeting (Box 66, Case 5, Audio-cassette 83-21)
      - 1983 Dec. 6-8: Southeast Women's Employment Coalition Board Meeting (Box 66, Case 5, Audio-cassette 83-22)
      - 1983 Dec. 6-8: Southeast Women's Employment Coalition Board Meeting (Box 66, Case 5, Audio-cassette 83-23)
      - 1983 Dec. 6-8: Southeast Women's Employment Coalition Board Meeting (Box 66, Case 5, Audio-cassette 83-24)